# **JASON P. CISNEROS**

(214) 516-2697 | Cisneros.Jason.P@gmail.com

# **PROFILE**

Hard-Working and motivated professional with nearly a decade of aircraft maintenance experience on US Air Force supporting fighter aircraft as well as 7 years of customer facing sales and support experience.

-- Qualifications: BS in Information Systems, AS in Science, professional military education, **active SECRET security clearance**. Experience in sales, customer service, troubleshooting, inspection, scheduled and unscheduled maintenance, safety practices, quality, situational awareness, and training.

#### **KEY SKILLS**

- EXCELLENT COMMUNICATOR SELF-MOTIVATED RESILIENCY MICROSOFT OFFICE
- FORWARD-THINKING ADAPTABLE PLANNING/ORGANIZING PROGRAMMING FAST LEARNER
- EXCELLENT COMPUTER SKILLS TECH-SAVVY INNOVATIVE PROBLEM-SOLVER DECISION MAKING

### **EXPERIENCE**

# United States Air Force Reserve -- NAS JRB Fort Worth, TX

Aircraft Armament Systems Technician | May 2011 to Present

- Inspected aircraft armament systems as well as perform reliability checks and troubleshooting.
- Adhered to aircraft specific technical orders in order to perform aircraft maintenance.
- Documented repairs and maintenance performed using computer-based data systems.
- Instructed members on how to safely and perform maintenance, inspections, and troubleshooting.

## **AT&T Mobility -- Richardson, TX**

Virtual Sales Expert & Retail Sales Consultant | December 2016 to Present

- Collaborated with coaches and teammates to develop and sales acumen and create solutions.
- Adapted to constantly changing sales goals and products to leverage the benefit of AT&T products.
- Managed and created accounts for customers using customer relation management systems and apps.
- Nominated to be team lead on first responders support program. FirstNet program. Promoted program.
- Effectively offer solutions to customers both in-store and remotely through video calls and phone calls.

### **Altex Computers & Electronics -- Carrollton, TX**

Technical Sales Representative | August 2013 to November 2015

- Led store in accomplishing an outstanding level of sales and amazing customer service experience.
- Worked directly with key decision makers to find networking solutions and place orders on accounts.
- Provided technical support for products sold both in store and remotely via e-mail and phone support.

#### **EDUCATION**

- University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington TX.

BS in Information Systems, Obtained May 2021

Emphasis in: Programming, Database Management, Networking, Data Analytics Programs, and Business.

- El Centro College, Dallas TX.

AS in Science, Obtained May 2019